Mr, Isaac Kelechi

Full Stack Developer

kcib.mail@gmail.com • 234 701 650 5681 • linkedin.com/in/kcib • kcib.netlify.app

Profile

Full Stack Developer with 5+ years of experience from creating, designing and managing web & mobile applications. Proficient with developing database, creating user interfaces, writing and testing code, debugging issues, implementing new features based on user feedback.

Professional Experience

Oct 2022 – Jan 2023 Lagos, Nigeria

Mobile App Developer, *Kreebz*

- Created a fully functional real estate mobile application.
- Implemented payment wallet into it.
- Collabed and communicated with the backend developer to connect the app to the database using Api

Jun 2021 – present Port Harcourt, Nigeria

Full Stack Developer, Quelib

- Created and implemented a full working mobile application from scratch to production with both back-end and front-end
- Marketed and Advertised the app via Facebook and Twitter and getting over 200% increase in users
- Push app to Google play store

Nov 2021 – Mar 2022 Ikeja Lagos, Nigeria

Mobile App Developer, FoodNow

- Identify, analyzed and debugged app issues with both back-end and front-end developers on the team.
- Recreated, Designed & maintained the app.
- Added a payment wallet, social system & Organizations

Nov 2020 – May 2021 Port Harcourt, Nigeria

Full Stack Developer, Ohms

- Created the wireframe and designed the app using flutter framework
- Developed the backend using php mysql and connected to the frontend using restful api

Skills

HTML CSS (Tailwind CSS, Styled-Component) JavaScript (JQuery) Flutter/Dart PHP Node.js (Express.js, Sequelize) React.js (TypeScript & Next.js) Firebase Git & Github MySql MongoDB Adobe illustrator Figma GraphQl & Rest Api Blockchain Heroku & Netlify Solidity

Education

Sep 2017 Bauchi, Nigeria Abubakar Tafewa Belewa University, Computer Science